FACING EL CHAPO
BASED ON TRUE EVENTS
JANUARY 6TH, 2016 7:00 AM
LOS MOCHIS, SINALOA
TWO TRUCKS FULL OF HITMEN CAME
TO THE HOUSE. THE THREE OF US ARE HERE.
HITMEN AT THE HOUSE.
THE THREE OF US ARE HERE.
JANUARY 8, 2016 10:32 AM
LOS MOCHIS, SINALOA
IN JULY 2019, JOAQUÍN GUZMÁN LOERA
WAS SENTENCED TO LIFE PLUS 30 YEARS
IVÁN GASTÉLUM WAS EXTRADITED TO THE U.S.
FOR DRUG TRAFFICKING AND FIREARM CRIMES.
ARTURO CARMONA WAS HONORED.
HE WAS THEN SENT
TO A FOREIGN SECURITY ROLE.
CARMONA AND HIS FAMILY
THEN RETURNED TO MEXICO.
HIS LOCATION AND IDENTITY
ARE CONFIDENTIAL.
HÉCTOR ROSALES WAS DECORATED
FOR HIS BRAVERY
AND SENT ABROAD WITH CARMONA.
HE DECIDED TO POSTPONE HIS RETIREMENT.
HIS WHEREABOUTS
AND IDENTITY REMAIN CLASSIFIED.
ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS
THIS FILM IS FOR YOU, LUCAS AND SILVESTRE
TO ALL MEMBERS OF PUBLIC ORDER FORCES
WHO UPHOLD THE RULE OF LAW IN OUR COUNTRY
TO THOSE WHO SUPPORT MY FILMS
AND THE HEROES FIGHTING FOR WHAT'S RIGHT.
SOME EVENTS, LOCATIONS,
AND CHARACTERS HAVE BEEN DRAMATIZED.